var questions = [
    {
        question: 'What will be the output of the following: console.log(2 + "2"); ?',
        choices: ['4', '22', '"22"', '"4"'],
        answer: '"22"',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the index of the first element in an array?',
        choices: ['0', '1', '-1', '10'],
        answer: '0',
    },
    {
        question: 'What keyword is used to return a value from a JavaScript function?',
        choices: ['value', 'result', 'return', 'output'],
        answer: 'return',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which keyword is used to refer to the current instance of a class inside its methods?',
        choices: ['self', 'this', 'it', 'current'],
        answer: 'this',
    },
    {
        question: 'Inside which HTML element do we put the Javascript?',
        choices: ['<js>', '<javascript>', '<script>', '<scripting>'],
        answer: '<script>',
    },
    {
        question: "What will be the output of the following: console.log('hi!'.length); ?",
        choices: ['hi!', '3', "'hi!' .length", '1'],
        answer: '3',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following data types are not commonly used?',
        choices: ['Strings', 'Boolean', 'Numbers', 'Alerts'],
        answer: 'Alerts',
    },
    {
        question: 'The ” var” and “function” are known as ?',
        choices: ['Data types', 'Keywords', 'Prototypes', 'Declaration Statements'],
        answer: 'Declaration Statements',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these symbols is used to create comments in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['//', '--', '^^', '{}'],
        answer: '//',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these keywords is used to define various functions in JavaScript?',
        choices: ['main', 'function', 'init', 'void'],
        answer: 'function',
    },
];
